unblockyoutube.co.uk 2008-02-19

# Privacy Policy

**Britster Ltd Privacy Policy  
**  
Protecting your privacy is important to Britster Ltd. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Britster Ltd Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. 

**Why we collect personal information**  
Britster Ltd collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. 

**How we collect personal information**  
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service. In addition, when you register with Britster Ltd or ask to be included in an email mailing list, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database. 

**When we disclose personal information  
**Britster Ltd gives shipping companies this information so they can deliver your products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies safeguard your personal information in accordance with Britster Ltd policies. 

At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information.

**How we protect your personal information  
**Britster Ltd safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

**Access to your personal information**  
You always have access to the information we have about you. If you would like to review personal information that Britster Ltd may have about you, email us at [data@britster.co.uk](mailto:data@britster.com)

**Collecting other personal information  
**When you browse Britster Ltd website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don’t collect personal information when you browse — not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using. 

In some of our emails to you, we use a “click-through URL.” When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. 

**Our companywide commitment to privacy**  
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Britster Ltd employee.

Britster Ltd website contains links to other sites. Britster Ltd does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. 

If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner. 

The Britster Ltd Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
